<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="croatian_tour_guide">Croatian Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="www_udacity_com">www.udacity.com</string>
    <string name="name_blue_cave"><![CDATA[BLUE CAVE & 6 ISLAND TOUR]]></string>
    <string name="name_blue_lagoon">BLUE LAGOON</string>
    <string name="name_hvar">SAIL HVAR ISLAND AND PAKLENI</string>
    <string name="name_dubrovnik">DUBROVNIK</string>
    <string name="description_blue_cave">f you want to discover Blue cave and 6 island experience this is a tour you should definitely do! You can spend a full day on the most attractive and breathtaking Dalmatian islands; our finest selections of the best island spots!</string>
    <string name="description_blue_lagoon">Blue Lagoon tour is perfect if you wish to avoid the crowds on the group tours, and have a relaxing and refreshing 5 hours out on beautiful coastal Croatia. Want to get away from Split but not waste an entire day?</string>
    <string name="description_hvar">This unforgettable excursion starts with a relaxed cruise on the mega catamaran to the beautiful bay on Šolta island. On the catamaran we’ll serve you welcome drinks, following with brunch and all inclusive drinks which are available until the end of the tour.</string>
    <string name="description_dubrovnik">Dubrovnik is a Croatian city on the Adriatic Sea. It is one of the most prominent tourist destinations in the Mediterranean Sea, a seaport and the centre of Dubrovnik-Neretva County. In 1979, the city of Dubrovnik joined the UNESCO list of World Heritage Sites.</string>
    <string name="wiki_blue_cave">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blue_Grotto_(Bi%C5%A1evo)</string>
    <string name="wiki_blue_lagoon">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Plava_Laguna</string>
    <string name="wiki_hvar">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hvar</string>
    <string name="wiki_dubrovnik">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dubrovnik</string>
    <string name="location_blue_cave">42.950000, 16.000000</string>
    <string name="location_blue_lagoon">45.206959, 13.589043</string>
    <string name="location_hvar">43.133333, 16.733333</string>
    <string name="location_dubrovnik">42.640278, 18.108333</string>
    <string name="name_durdevac">Old town Đurđevac</string>
    <string name="name_eltz">Eltz Manor</string>
    <string name="name_ilok">Ilok Castle</string>
    <string name="name_kastilac">Kaštilac</string>
    <string name="name_pejacevic">Pejačević Castle in Virovitica</string>
    <string name="description_pejacevic">Pejačević Castle in Virovitica is a late-baroque and neoclassicistic castle in the town of Virovitica, Virovitica–Podravina County, northern Croatia. It is one of several castles owned by the members of Pejačević noble family in the region of Slavonia.</string>
    <string name="description_kastilac">Kaštilac was a fortress of a Benedictine Monastery located by the Adriatic Sea in central Dalmatia, and is now a settlement in Kaštel Gomilica, located in the central part of Split-Dalmatia county, Croatia. Kaštilac is the only castle of seven castles in Kaštela.</string>
    <string name="ilok">Ilok Castle or Odescalchi Castle overlooks the town of Ilok in eastern Croatia. It is built on a hill above the town centre, offering views on the Danube and the Pannonian Plain.</string>
    <string name="description_eltz">Eltz Manor is a Baroque castle in Vukovar, Croatia. The 18th-century manor is the location of the Vukovar City Museum. The manor, as it previously appeared, is depicted on the reverse of the Croatian 20 kuna banknote, issued in 1993 and 2001. The castle was destroyed in 1991 in the Croatian War of Independence. However, after four years of restorations, it was completely restored to its pre-war appearance in October 2011.</string>
    <string name="description_durdevac">Old town Đurđevac was built by the Bishop of Pécs, most probably around 1488. The town, or fort, was built on high ground in the middle of a swamp to the north of the town of Đurđevac in Croatia, because of the threat of the Turkish, and constant conflicts between the nobility. The height of the tower is around 30 feet (9 m).</string>
    <string name="wiki_durdevac">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Old_town_%C4%90ur%C4%91evac</string>
    <string name="wiki_eltz">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eltz_Manor</string>
    <string name="wiki_ilok">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ilok_Castle</string>
    <string name="wiki_kastilac">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ka%C5%A1tilac</string>
    <string name="wiki_pejacevic">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peja%C4%8Devi%C4%87_Castle_in_Virovitica</string>
    <string name="location_pejacevic">45.833790, 17.385466</string>
    <string name="location_kastilac">43.547239, 16.395369</string>
    <string name="location_ilok">45.224038, 19.375361</string>
    <string name="location_eltz">45.357536, 18.994986</string>
    <string name="location_durdevac">46.045000, 17.068000</string>
    <string name="adriatic_sea">Adriatic Sea</string>
    <string name="name_plitvice">Plitvice Lakes National Park</string>
    <string name="name_brijuni">Brijuni</string>
    <string name="name_krka">Krka National Park</string>
    <string name="name_velebit">Northern Velebit National Park</string>
    <string name="description_velebit">The Northern Velebit National Park is a national park in Croatia that covers 109 km2 of the northern section of the Velebit mountains, the largest mountain range in Croatia. Because of the abundant variety of this part of the Velebit range, the area was upgraded from a nature reserve[2] in 1999, and opened as a national park in September the same year.</string>
    <string name="description_krka">Krka National Park is one of the Croatian national parks, named after the river Krka (ancient Greek: Kyrikos) that it encloses. It is located along the middle-lower course of the Krka River in central Dalmatia, in Šibenik-Knin county, downstream Miljevci area, and just a few kilometers northeast of the city of Šibenik.</string>
    <string name="description_brijuni">The Brijuni are a group of fourteen small islands in the Croatian part of the northern Adriatic Sea, separated from the west coast of the Istrian peninsula by the narrow Fažana Strait.</string>
    <string name="description_plitvice">Plitvice Lakes National Park is one of the oldest and the largest national park in Croatia. In 1979, Plitvice Lakes National Park was added to the UNESCO World Heritage register.</string>
    <string name="wiki_plitvice">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Plitvice_Lakes_National_Park</string>
    <string name="wiki_brijuni">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brijuni</string>
    <string name="wiki_krka">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Krka_National_Park</string>
    <string name="wiki_velebit">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Northern_Velebit_National_Park</string>
    <string name="location_velebit">44.693056, 15.006944</string>
    <string name="location_krka">43.801944, 15.972778</string>
    <string name="location_brijuni">44.916667, 13.766667</string>
    <string name="location_plitvice">44.880556, 15.616111</string>
    <string name="name_zagreb">Archaeological Museum in Zagreb</string>
    <string name="name_osijek">Archaeological Museum Osijek</string>
    <string name="name_mestrovic">Ivan Meštrović Gallery</string>
    <string name="name_croatian_natural">Croatian Natural History Museum</string>
    <string name="description_croatian_natural">The Croatian Natural History Museum is the oldest and biggest natural history museum and the main body for natural history research, preservation and collection in Croatia. Located on Dimitrije Demeter Street in Gornji Grad, one of the oldest neighbourhoods of the Croatian capital Zagreb, it owns one of the biggest museum collections in Croatia, with over 2 million artefacts, including over 1.1 million animal specimens.</string>
    <string name="description_mestrovic">Ivan Meštrović Gallery is an art museum in Split, Croatia dedicated to the work of the 20th-century sculptor, Ivan Meštrović. The gallery preserves and presents to the public the most significant works of Meštrović, and is in itself an art monument.</string>
    <string name="description_osijek">Archaeological Museum Osijek is an archaeological museum in Osijek, Croatia. It is located in Tvrđa.</string>
    <string name="description_zagreb">The Archaeological Museum in Zagreb, Croatia is an archaeological museum with over 450,000 varied artifacts and monuments, gathered from various sources but mostly from Croatia and in particular from the surroundings of Zagreb.</string>
    <string name="wiki_zagreb">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Archaeological_Museum_in_Zagreb</string>
    <string name="wiki_osijek">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Archaeological_Museum_Osijek</string>
    <string name="wiki_mestrovic">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ivan_Me%C5%A1trovi%C4%87_Gallery</string>
    <string name="wiki_croatian_natural">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Croatian_Natural_History_Museum</string>
    <string name="location_croatian_natural">45.817115, 15.972314</string>
    <string name="location_mestrovic">43.504306, 16.417917</string>
    <string name="location_osijek">45.560833, 18.695278</string>
    <string name="location_zagreb">45.811111, 15.977222</string>
    <string name="castles">Castles</string>
    <string name="national_parks">National parks</string>
    <string name="museum">Museum</string>
</resources>
